(Bernadette:)Can I ask you something?
(Bernadette:)Why do you constantly feel
the need to put down my husband?
(Penny:)I'm sure he does it out of love.
(Penny:)The same way my boyfriend
makes me feel terrible
(Penny:)about my life choices.
(Amy:)I think we're gonna go.
(Leonard:)No, no. This is not a fight.
(Leonard:)I was just excited that
someone offered you a part
(Leonard:)and a little surprised
that you'd rather sit at home
(Leonard:)and do nothing than take it.
(Leonard:)Now it's a fight.
(Sheldon:)Well, with that sorted out,
(Sheldon:)I'm happy to answer your
question, Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)Howard started it.
(Howard:)I didn't do anything.
I was just sitting here.
(Sheldon:)I wasn't referring to this evening.
(Sheldon:)Ten years ago,
upon first seeing me,
(Sheldon:)your husband claimed
that I looked like C-3PO
(Sheldon:)and Pee-wee Herman.
(Sheldon:)And he called me
C-3P-wee Herman.
(Raj:)Still funny.